Muhammad Amin Igbaal Alam, S.Kom

System Analyst

I am Muhammad Amin Iqbaal Alam, S.Kom graduate Bachelor Degree of Informatics Engineering Brawijaya University. I have experience in developing software. Having knowledge of enterprise business systems such as ERP (Enterprise Resource Planning) like SAP, government services, telecommunication services, e-commerce, company profile, state-owned enterprise services, hospital management information system (SIMRS) dan Electronic Medical Records. I am a well-organized person and detail oriented. especially web based and mobile based. I am a disciplined person, can work in a team or individually and adapt to the environment.



aminiqbaal@outlook.com / iqbaal.project86@gmail.com in

Muhammad Amin Iqbaal Alam





Work Experience

Software Engineer Internship PT. Avemedia Nusantara

April 2019-Juli2019 Malang, East Java

System Analyst & Software Engineer CV. Pastijadi Digital Solutions

Jul 2019-Jan 2022 Surabaya, East Java

Software Engineer PT. Patigeni Mitra Sejati

Feb 2022-Aug 2022 Semarang, Central Java

System Support & Front End Developer RSUD Dr. Soetomo Jawa Timur

October 2022-December 2022 Surabaya, East Java

ICT Engineer - System & **Business Analyst**

Website & Mobile Android development using Trello, PHP, CodeIgniter (HMVC), Android Java, and MySQL, Trello, Bitbucket

- Website Quick Count Pemilu 2018 Kab. Lamongan
- Website Registrasi Digital PT. Sampoerna
- Application Android Registrasi Digital PT. Sampoerna

Documentation Functional Specification Document (FSD), Technical Specification Document (TSD), Business Requirement Document (BRD), User Acceptance Test (UAT), System Integration Testing (SIT), UI/UX Designer, analysis and testing using Trello Visual Paradigm, Draw.io, Bizagi Modeler, Figma, PHP, Laravel and Selenium

- E-commerce Raprima Tempeh (CRM)
- Donation Ponpes Bahrul Maghfiroh
- · News Portal
- Consultation Lawyer

Website & Mobile Android / iOS development using Trello, PHP, Laravel, Flutter, and MySQL, Trello, Bitbucket

- Website Firecek (CRM)
- Website Sticker Generator
- Application Android & iOS Firecek (CRM)

Documentation, UI/UX Designer and analysis using Visual Paradigm, Draw.io, Bizagi Modeler, Figma, VueJS, Laravel, Kanban

- Company Profile RSUD Dr. Soetomo
- Helpdesk ITKI (Instalasi Teknologi Komunikasi dan Informasi)
- Sismaker (Sistem Manajemen Keperawatan) (CRM)

Documentation Blueprint, Functional Specification Document (FSD), Technical Specification Document (TSD), Business

PT. Garuda Maintenance Facility AeroAsia (Garuda Indonesia Group)

Jan 2023 - Dec 2023 Tangerang, Banten Requirement Document (BRD), User Acceptance Test (UAT), System Integration Testing (SIT), Business Case, UI/UX Designer and analysis using Visual Paradigm, Draw.io, PlantUML, Figma, Prisma, DB Diagram, SAP, Bitbucket

- Dashboard XPREAM Unit TV (CRM)
- Excellent Project Management Stream (CRM)
- Budget Realization
- Instrumentation Measurement Tools and Equipment
- GSMART
- · Hold Item List
- ICT Project Management Office
- Analytic Report Component (ARC)
- IERApps for Production Units Tools & Equipments

System Analyst PT. Ako Media Asia (SALT Indonesia)

Dec 2023 - Jun 2024 West Jakarta, DKI Jakarta Documentation & Analysist Business Requirement Document (BRD), Interface Agreement Document (IFA), Product requirement document (PRD) Technical requirement use Brainstorming, Software Requirement Specification (SRS), Non-Fungible Token (NFT) Document, Penetretation Testing Document, Domain Driven Design, API Contract, Use Case, Sequence Diagram use Visual Studio Code, Draw.io, Postman, PlantUML

- MyOrbit Telkomsel (CRM)
 - · Recurring by Pulsa
 - Revamp Homepage (Prepaid & Postpaid Modem)
 - Revamp Productpage (Prepaid & Postpaid Modem)
 - Blog
 - Prepaid Registration I-Setup
 - Filter Modem
 - I-Join (Prepaid & Postpaid Modem)
 - Notification MSISDN Forwarding & Simplify

Front-End Mobile Applications Developer Borneo Intech

Feb 2022 - Juli 2024 Remote Development mobile application base java android use android studio

Borneojek

Pendidikan

2016 - 2022

Brawijaya University Informatics Engineering

Skills

• PostgreSQL & MySQL (Database)

- Draw.io & PlantUML (Diagram)
- Figma (UI/UX Design)

Certificates

- Basic Android For Beginner by Pintaar
- Basic React.js for Beginner by Pintaar
- Basic Vue.js for Beginner by Pintaar

- Corel Draw (Design)
- Prisma.io (Dabatase Design)
- Dbeaver (Dabatase Design)
- Domain Driven Design
- SAP ABAP (ERP)
- Mobile (Flutter & Java)
- API Contract
- Event Storming
- PHP (Laravel & CodeIgniter)
- Javascripst (VueJS, ReactJS)

- TOEFL Score 557 by English Domestics
- Health, Safety, and Environment by PT. Freeport Indonesia
- Basic Flutter for Beginner by Pintaar
- Front End Development Fundamental Media Management Training by NU Online
- Microsoft Office Desktop Application by Brawijaya University
- .Net (dotnet) Angular for E-Commerce by Udemy (on Going)
- Ahli K3 Umum by Mita Indonesia Berdaya

Powered by CakeResume